Come on, we're shining, running, forever!
The sea is calling out, so ride the waves!
We're all together as one,
so let's sail in the sun!
All our dreams are never ending, so
let's wake up, wake up, wake up, wake up!
Heartbeat, we will be one! Go ahead!
Even though our hearts have
traveled different paths.
We are best friends.
Our freedom is our only compass.
That's pointing us along the
many roads that come together.
We will keep on running forward every day.
Go east, go west.
As long as we keep looking to the horizon.
We'll see everything all crystal clear.
We're all so thrilled that we
can't wait until the dawn arrives.
So we'll just bring the
sun ourselves to know.
If the winds blow, we're waiting
where we should be going, go?
That's right. We're
shining, running forever.
All of our dreams will
merge into one piece.
No matter where we go,
we'll be fine and free.
Cause all our treasure is our strength.
Come on, we're shining, running forever.
The sea is coming out, so ride the wave.
We're all together as well.
So let's just stay with the sun.
While our dreams are never ending.
Heartbeat, we will be one, go ahead.
My darkness will swallow the world.
Just you wait and see.
You think I'll lose to you?
I'm gonna be king of the pirates
Roger's treasure belongs to me
We'll ride non-stop and travel farther
than we've ever gone And then tomorrow
we will find suspense And then commence
to live out another day so intense
That's right, we're shining,
Running forever. Let's go along
with curiosity. Our feelings lead
the way straight to a brand new day Into
another adventure Come on, we're shining,
running forever Open the map inside your
heart and see No matter where we end up,
our mods will never give up There's a fire
in our dreams And you can never, never,
never, never stop it We
will be one, go ahead
Where now?
We'll show you.
There's an underground tunnel that
connects Greenbit to Dressrosa.
We finally made it!
There's the airport!
Oh, wow!
This is way nicer than I expected!
Goodness, isn't that cute?
Yellow Caboo 43 buzzing in!
I'm ready for takeoff!
Yellow Caboo 43, you're
cleared for takeoff!
Pink Bee Squad here,
we're ready when you are!
Roger that, Pink Bee!
All bug units stand by
for further instruction!
Oh, and Usulin, please watch your step among
the aircraft. Oh, sorry. Hey, you guys!
I'm here!
Leo!
It's about time!
Preparation's complete.
Let's take to the air, shall we?
I'm counting on you, okay? Don't worry.
This is exactly what our squad members
have been tirelessly training to tackle.
This is definitely a first.
I gotta show Luffy.
You aren't as compact as we are.
You'll have to hop aboard our special
20-passenger buses, if you don't mind.
Uh-huh.
Linear foxes, please report in. Oh!
This isn't bad.
We're gonna ride in style.
They're really fast, too.
Such beautiful fur.
It's time to take flight, everybody!
With Usuland beside us,
there's no way we can lose!
We'll bring our friends back
and Princess Monchery, too!
Yeah!
I suppose I should explain
why we want to do this.
What are you doing in there, perv?
She's got you.
Oh, yes, at your service.
And thank you for the best
seat on the bus, my dear.
Since you're generous enough to
lay down your lives for our cause,
there's something that I
think you should know first.
I don't remember promising that.
Doflamingo has caused a great deal of
suffering, especially for the Tantata tribe.
But our troubled
relationship with his group
actually began long before
he took over the throne.
In fact, the beginning of this sad
tale stretches back over 900 years.
What?
Here in Dressrosa, there grows
a vast field of sunflowers.
And somewhere, nestled among those
blooms, in an unknown location,
there is a secret entrance.
Follow the winding spiral
staircase deep into the ground,
and a cacophony of excited
voices can be heard.
Allow me to introduce you.
The commander!
We've waited so long!
We're glad you finally made it!
Thank you. At ease.
Hooray!
Who's that Tom Tump-looking guy, sir?
It'll be great to have a big
person like him on our side, huh?
There's no way we'll lose the battle now.
Those are the little people from Tontata.
They will be fighting
Doflamingo with us. Say what?
They're more of a threat than
you might think, my friend.
They move so fast,
they're almost invisible.
The townspeople call them fairies.
Ah!
Wait, so when Zorro's
sword disappeared before...
Come on!
I thought you wanted to
get back to your ship!
Huh?
Damn, Luffy, get it together!
Young man, will you please sit down? Huh?
That sneaky little bastard.
There's a fighting competition
and he doesn't bother telling me.
I could have cleaned up!
Ah! Commander! Huh?
You're here too?
I'm just as surprised to see you, buddy.
Commander!
We've already reviewed the
intel from the scouting unit!
We know everything that Sugar and
the enemy have been up to, sir.
And, as it turns out, just in time for
our big confrontation with Doflamingo!
Also,
some legendary heroes have appeared in our
kingdom and they're
going to help us fight!
Uh, their names are Usaland and Robaland!
They're on their way here as we speak!
And they've got a whole group
of friends here with them, too!
Let's see...
It says their names are Luffy-Land,
Zora-Land, Nami-Land, Son-Land, Chopper-Land,
Fra-Land, and Bone-Land!
Sounds like Usopp.
That's the best he could come up with?
Uh, okay, I'm Zora-Land, I guess.
And I'm the famous Fra-Land,
here to save the day!
Wow, that's great!
I don't have time for this!
I have to get back to the
sunny before it's too late!
I have been saying that this whole time!
It's no use.
You can't stifle my artistic expression.
Now, blow, kung fu.
This is just smoke.
Well, two can play that game.
Try my weather icon for size.
Snow clouds fill the sky now.
Ah, my poor climate attack.
You turned it into some weird toy!
My oh my!
No need to flatter me,
my dear. Like I would!
Well, as beautiful as it may be,
that staff of yours is not a toy.
Make no mistake! Oh,
there is a Devil Fruit
user in the Don Quixote
family who can transform people into toys.
I possess the power of the
art art fruit, remember?
The masterpieces I create
aren't toys at all. Huh? Oh no!
Nami can't fight her!
And with bunny rabbits for hooves,
there's not much I can do either.
Help me, I'm scared.
Please don't let her take me away.
She'll have to pry you
from my cold, dead hands.
Oh, unfortunately.
With no guitar, that might
be a very real possibility.
You act as though this
is some sort of tragedy.
You should be thrilled.
I'm making you art.
This is your doing, after all.
You were the ones who went
and obliterated my submarine.
My poor henchmen.
I must avenge them.
I guarantee you, your death
will be quite the spectacle!
Hello, it's Chopper! Who's there?
Whoever you are, we need your help!
Please hurry!
Who told you you could answer that?
Listen, Raccoon.
Whatever your situation is, I don't care!
Huh?
It's Traffy! Huh?
Oh, hello, law.
What would you say that for?
Come help us, you jerk.
It's hard to explain, but we're
artwork now, and it's just terrible.
Well, I'm all right, but please come.
Look, take the ship.
And head for Greenbit now.
I want to leave Caesar with you.
Just come to Greenbit. Calic.
How could he hang up like that?
I thought he already gave them, Caesar.
He didn't even listen
to what we had to say.
It was just like talking to Luffy.
Oh, this is bad.
This is the end of the line, Law.
Who did you just call?
Might as well go ahead and
give me Caesar's heart.
Haven't you done enough scurrying
around like a miserable rat?
I set a trap for your little partner,
and wouldn't you know it, that
genius has walked right into it!
I knew he wouldn't be able to resist that
gladiator contest at Corita Coliseum.
All the competitors are dangerous
outlaws ready to fight to the death.
Just stepping into the
ring is a suicide mission.
Straw Hat doesn't stand a chance.
I'm sure they're scraping
him off the wall as we speak.
Your alliance has fallen apart.
So?
Are you ready to give up?
Fight valiantly, Sir Luffy.
There's no time for spectating, but he
mustn't lose his honor is at stake after all?
It's Buggy. I heard things
were heating up around here.
Yeah, hey, who's the small fry?
Now for my Gum-Gum Hawk Rifle!
Whoa, here it comes!
Yeah-ho-ho, not bad for a twerp.
All I gotta do is win Ace's fruit,
so I'm not done yet. Got it?
Yo-ho-ho, now that's a good joke.
There's no chance. Give up!
You're nothing but
children drunk on infamy.
They call you the worst generation,
but you're not strong enough to sail across
the ocean your forebearers fought upon.
After Whitebeard's death,
it was the end of an era.
In fact,
the only pirate from your generation with
even a sliver of
potential is Blackbeard T.
Blackbeard?
Well, perhaps time will tell.
But face it.
If you're only able to match me in terms
of strength in my current lowly state,
you don't stand a chance.
Just throw in the towel already.
Like I already said, you're
not a shabby opponent.
But if Rayleigh chose a brat like you
as a flag bearer for the new generation,
he's not as sharp as he used to be.
The Navy, on the other
hand, they were wise.
Fire Fist, he had the devil's
blood flowing in his veins.
They stamped him just in time.
You think you can beat the Navy
Admirals and four Emperors?
And somehow surpass
Roger's legacy as well?
Don't make me laugh. No one can.
It's impossible.
Then just watch me!
Gum-Gum ROCKET! Wait!
Is he flying?
What an incredibly high leap!
All right, boy.
Time for your final lesson.
I've been holding onto 30
years of rage towards Garp.
Now it's time to collect, Straw Hats,
in the form of an Alto KO Skull Smash!
Damn it!
What the hell's going on with this ice?
It doesn't melt.
Axes won't break it.
So what do we do?
Of course there's an unbelievable
amount of pirate treasure under it,
just out of our reach!
Yeah, ho ho!
You could try for a hundred years.
You wouldn't make a scratch
in the ice with those tools.
If you want to shatter it, then you must
apply tremendous pressure in one spot.
Drill, Dragoneel!
Watch this!
Open, Chinchou!
Boys tie up these wannabe treasure thieves
and throw them into the ocean. Right?
Will do.
So many riches—the entirety of my life's
work is held safely
within this cage of ice.
Hope for the future, joy
and sorrow of the past,
all told in centuries worth
of my family's treasures.
And the only key to the
room is my drill head.
Without it, there's no way to get.
get
inside.
Nobody can invade my
sanctuary, not even the Navy.
Today's the day.
I've been doing some
training to found in that big
head of yours, Ching Chow.
Polarized eight mountains down to sand to
get ready for this moment.
Prepare yourself.
Your bluster and no bite, Garp.
There's nothing in the world
that's harder than my head!
Drill, get ready to eat those words.
This mighty head of mine
will split your fist in two!
Hear me!
No way!
He actually did it!
Let's get out of here!
Oh shit, it's set sail!
You had us scared for a second there.
I said open Xin Zhao
Drill, drag, and nail
Open Xin Zhao. Just open up.
It won't open
What can I do? All my
treasure lost. Right.
in front of me just
out of reach everything
i've worked for sealed
away an endless fortune
Damn you, God. You will
pay for this curse.
your children and grandchildren to curse
you for all eternity
bastard a short time
after that I retired gave up pirating my
power was gone and my
heart broken into pieces
What the fuck?
Where am I hallucinating?
Lucy's arm is implanted like a balloon.
Witness me, Garp.
I'm about to take your
precious grandson's life.
You hear me?
Straw Hat,
it's time for you to pay for
your old man's right hook
that took everything away
from me and destroyed my life.
A punch?
That's why you're so bent out of shape?
Come on!
I can't even remember how many
times I got slugged by him!
Then I'll finish the job and
pulverize every bone in your body!
Ashokan, Jack Peek!
Get ready for my Gum-Gum!
Non-drill dragon!
Elephant gun!
Non-nail!
Gramps, are you dead?
Wait, he's out.
Xin Zhao is eliminated.
This round's winner is Lucy!
This is simply remarkable!
He bested a living legend!
After a hard-fought battle, we
have a champion for Block Z!
Let's hear it for Lucy!
Yeah!
I admit I never expected
him to go this far.
Who can have predicted a
surprise ending like this?
Listen to all those idiots cheer him on.
I'm sick of this Lucy crap.
Even under a false name,
he gets the limelight.
But now that the match
is done, you're mine.
And this time, you're dead.
Are you deaf, Cavendish?
I'm not going to let you touch him.
No freaking way.
You get in my way and I'll
kill you as well, Bartolomeo.
I'd like to see you try!
I'm the one to kill Straw Hat.
He coupled a legend, but can
he hold on to this momentum?
And if not Lucy,
who will go on to win the championship
and take home the flame flame fruit?
I get it.
This should be interesting.